There is another sector for which currency is
favourable, otherwise nothing else is favourable and
that is IT companies. The exchange results of America's leading IT
companies are fine, but the
third grade given by the company for the future
and the guidance given for the whole year has
spoiled the mood. Kushal Gupta who
tracks the IT sector is here to
tell us all this, tell us all the details, Kushal, it is going to
spoil the mood 100% Sir, the
kind of numbers that Accenture has given, fourthly,
they are as per the shameful estimates, but the
focus was on the guidance only, and
on the guidance, the company is saying that
their revenue estimates going forward are as
estimated by the analysts,
especially for Q1 F5 23, compared to the estimates of 16.07 billion by
the annals,
they have given guidance of
only 15.2 billion dollars, that is, the
high range guidance is also
less than the analyst's estimate, so this clearly
indicates that going forward  The
impact may be
on client budget spending,
which could lead to a
slight slowdown in revenue growth momentum going forward. In fact, the
way
IT expenses are likely to be cut in the future, it could
also have an impact on margins, which is
why they have given margin
guidance in the range of 15.3% to 15.5% for the full year. In fact, there is a
negative forex impact in dollar
terms. They have put the biggest impact on this.
They are expecting a negative forex impact of around 8-30%
because the way the dollar index
is rising and all the IT companies
that have exposure in different countries outside that, the
forex impact could be
big there because all other currencies are
obviously losing value due to the
rising US dollar. So, definitely because of this,
this impact will be a big one going forward.  So,
regarding the demand structure and also the currency
negative forex impact, it will be
seen coming and that is why the extension
guidance and IT outs have fallen here, okay, so
this weak guidance of the exchange and
you are seeing its effect, all the
companies are good from Siddharth ji's perspective, the
outlook is still good, should not buy or
stay away from ittiano sir, if you like, then what should you
buy
because I think that
amidst these clouds of negative news, now there is an
opportunity to choose the stocks well
and that company which is Prince
Performance and that company is Persistent
Systems because it is performing consistently very well,
if you look at the results of the last quarter, you will see that other
companies are so weak and
along with buying such strong supporting systems, if you want to
buy something as a CP or as a lampsome, then
I think there is only one
company whose guidance
is the best in the entire Halo,
due to the impact of Aldo Exact, there will be some
guidance up and down,
even for Infosys, but Infosys is an excellent company, as well as
Persistent.  The system that should be bought is
Persistent System and Infosys, I have
bought both of them, they have
shown some action yesterday also.